Here we are using an invisible table to
align the labels and entry fields, like
this, date, colon, answer here, first
name, colon, answer here, and last name,
colon, answer here. And you can see this
by going to the table design and actually
showing the borders. So while this looks
neat visually, it creates a major problem
for accessibility. For people who use
screen readers, the software doesn't see a
simple form. Instead, it announces table
with two rows and four columns, then they
have to navigate cell by cell, reading out
row one, column three, date, then row one,
column four, answer here. A much better
and simpler approach is to remove the
table entirely and just use line breaks.
So the form just ends up being date,
colon, enter, first name, colon, enter,
and last name, colon, enter on separate
lines, like this. And now I can delete the
form or
delete the table, and we end up with a
simple, the simplest design.